D A V E D E S C H E N E A U X

LOS ANGELES



FULL STACK
WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT ME



DAVEDESCH@GMAIL.COM

GITHUB.COM/DAVEDESCH LINKEDIN.COM/IN/DDESCH DAVEDESCH.GITHUB.IO

TECH SKILLS



RUBY ON RAILS

JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY

HTML/CSS

GIT

AGILE DEVELOPMENT

SQL

POSTGRESQL



ABOUT ME

I love being a web developer. I was previously in the hospitality industry specializing in nightclubs and restaurants. In 2014, I decided to make a major career change and attended a coding boot camp to learn Ruby on Rails. I am constantly learning new things independently and brushing up on my fundamentals.



EXPERIENCE

O DIRECTOR OF OPERATIONS MAY 2007 - NOV 2014
LOW FREQUENCY MANAGEMENT

Planned and facilitated nightclub events for up to 1000 guests.

Managed and staffed multiple venues throughout the metro Detroit area.

RESEARCH ASSISTANT JAN 2009 - DEC 2010
NORTHWESTERN MUTUAL

Implemented existing market research for client presentations.

Researched and analyzed data for existing and potential clients.



PROJECTS

O ENSEMBLE - TEAM LEAD
RAILS, HTML/CSS, JAVASCRIPT

A FASHION APP TO GET FEEDBACK ON WHAT YOU'RE WEARING AND SEE WHAT OTHERS ARE WEARING

MYENSEMBLE.IO



EDUCATION

O DEV BOOTCAMP OCT 2014 - MAR 2015
APPRENTICE

19-week intensive boot camp focusing on Ruby on Rails and JavaScript.

D EASTERN MICHIGAN OCT 2010 - JUNE 2013
POLITICAL SCIENCE

Statistical Analysis Public Policy Analysis